jounce.com 2014-11-20

# Privacy Statement - Instapage

At INSTAPAGE, we value the trust you place in us and take your privacy seriously. We want to let you know what information we collect when you use our products and services, why we collect it and how we use it to improve your experience. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the INSTAPAGE website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy covers INSTAPAGE's treatment of personal information that INSTAPAGE gathers when you are on the INSTAPAGE website and when you use INSTAPAGE services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that INSTAPAGE does not own or control, or to people that INSTAPAGE does not employ or manage. 

## Personal Responsibility

You should inform yourself regarding safe internet practices and what you can do to protect yourself against identity theft and Internet Fraud. The federal government and technology industry have developed practical tips to help you guard against Internet fraud, secure your computer and protect your personal information. You can learn more about practical online safety tips at https://www.onguardonline.gov. For your privacy and security, your INSTAPAGE account information is protected by a password. You should always log off once you have finished using a shared computer to protect against unauthorized access to your password and/or computer. 

## Collection & Use of Information by INSTAPAGE

INSTAPAGE collects personal information when you use INSTAPAGE products or services, when you register with INSTAPAGE, and when you visit INSTAPAGE web pages or the web pages of INSTAPAGE partners. INSTAPAGE may combine the information that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 

**For example:**  
When you register with INSTAPAGE and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. In order for you to use certain INSTAPAGE services, you must complete a registration form. As part of this registration form, we require certain personal information, such as your name, city, state, zip code, and e-mail address. Also, whenever you interact with us, we automatically collect certain information whether or not you register with INSTAPAGE. For example, INSTAPAGE automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, INSTAPAGE cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request. INSTAPAGE also collects information regarding service surveys, feedback forms, support forums and other text services you use or post. INSTAPAGE uses the information it collects to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends, and to administer the website. INSTAPAGE also use the information to conduct research, customize advertising and content, improve our services, improve product and service offerings, provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients, and to contact you. 

## E-mail

INSTAPAGE will not provide your email address to a third party without your express permission. If you register with INSTAPAGE, we may send out e-mails with INSTAPAGE-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, follow the instructions provided in the unwanted e-mail message or visit the Email Preferences section of your User Account and change the settings. Please note that changing your Email Preferences will not prevent you from receiving system e-mails (e.g., those regarding forgotten user names or passwords) and legal notices (e.g., policy updates). 

## Cookies

INSTAPAGE transfers cookies (alphanumeric identifiers) to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable INSTAPAGE to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. INSTAPAGE cookies do not collect personal information. INSTAPAGE does not use cookie information with other personal information to tell us your screen name, e-mail address, or who you are. You may set your browser to fully disable cookies or to notify you when you receive a new cookie. The "Help" button on most browsers will explain how to change your cookie settings. However, to use certain INSTAPAGE features the INSTAPAGE cookie must remain activated. We recommend that you leave the INSTAPAGE cookie activated. 

Please note that advertisers and other third-parties may use cookies on our website. We do not control or have access to these cookies. 

## Information Sharing & Disclosure

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. Also, we limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices. INSTAPAGE does not sell, rent, or share personal information about you with non-affiliated companies or other people except to provide products or services you have requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of INSTAPAGE's Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, and may share information to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. If a INSTAPAGE user is a child under age 13, we may share information with a parent's authorization. Parents may allow INSTAPAGE to collect and use their child's information without consenting to INSTAPAGE's sharing of this information with companies and people who may use the information for their own purposes. INSTAPAGE may display targeted advertisements based on personal information. It is possible that advertisers will assume that people who click or interact with targeted ads meet the targeting criteria. INSTAPAGE does not provide advertisers any personal information when you view or interact with a targeted ad. 

INSTAPAGE personnel may have access to information in the normal course of INSTAPAGE's business. Trusted partners who work with INSTAPAGE under confidentiality agreements may also have access to information. These companies do not have any independent right to share this information. Likewise, authorized INSTAPAGE consultants and/or contractors may also have access to user information, if necessary, in the normal course of INSTAPAGE's business. If INSTAPAGE merges with another company or if INSTAPAGE or substantially all of the assets of its Website or business relating to INSTAPAGE services are acquired by or transferred to another company, then information may be transferred is such a merger or acquisition. 

## Children Under 18 Years of Age

Children under the age of 13 may not register to use the INSTAPAGE website. INSTAPAGE does not specifically collect information about children. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask and receive their parents' permission before using INSTAPAGE or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet. 

## Changes to Privacy Policy

INSTAPAGE may update this policy. You will be notified of significant changes either by an email to the primary email address provided by you in your INSTAPAGE account or by placement of an announcement on the INSTAPAGE website. The Privacy Policy in effect at the time information is used shall apply to that use. 

## Conditions of Use

Your visit to INSTAPAGE's website and any dispute over privacy is subject to our Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, including limitations on damages and application of Utah state law, jurisdiction and venue.
